tpackaging.com 2016-09-06

# Privacy Policy - Burlington, ON - Transparent Packaging

**Transparent Packaging Inc.** respects your privacy and our site visitors' information. We do not share, sell, or rent any of the information collected to any third parties and do not intend to do so in the future.

**Information Collected**  
If you request or submit information to us by sending an Email via [info@tpackaging.com](mailto:info@tpackaging.com) or by filling out a "contact" form, we may save your Email address as well as any other information you provide. This information may be used to contact you in the future by mail, Email, or phone to convey information about our solutions or services that we feel may benefit you. Your Email and other information will not be sold to any third party.

**Information Collected by Others**  
This notice addresses only Transparent Packaging Inc.'s website policy, and does not apply to sites that users access via links from our site. Transparent Packaging Inc. is not responsible for the information collecting policies of other sites, for the practices employed by websites linked to or from our website, or for the information or content contained therein. Often, links to other websites are provided solely on the basis that they may contain useful information for our visitors. Users are advised to review the privacy policy of other websites.

**Cookies**  
Transparent Packaging Inc.'s website does not use cookies.

**Updating, Correcting, and Deleting Personal Information**  
If you would like to have your personal information removed from our records, please send an Email with "Remove personal information" in the subject line.

**Legally Compelled Disclosure of Information**  
Transparent Packaging Inc. may disclose information when legally compelled to do so: when we, in good faith, believe that the law requires us to do so or for the protection of our legal rights.

**Periodic Policy Changes**  
Please note that Transparent Packaging Inc. reviews its privacy practices from time-to-time (i.e. to track technology and/or legal changes), and that these practices are subject to change. To ensure continuing familiarity with the most current version of our privacy policy, please bookmark and periodically review this page.

This policy statement is made in the name of Transparent Packaging Inc. and is effective as of September 14, 2011. This statement does not create an agreement between Transparent Packaging Inc. and users, and as such, does not create any legal rights for any party.

**Contact Us:  
Transparent Packaging Inc.**  
3380 South Service Rd.  
Burlington, ON L7N 3J5

Phone: 905-632-8722  
Fax: 905-632-1458  
Email: [info@tpackaging.com](mailto:info@tpackaging.com)  
Website: [www.tpackaging.com](http://www.tpackaging.com/)
